Ms. Thant Mon Naing — Mobile Application Developer

- ★ Date of Birth 11 August, 1995
- ★ thantmonnaing@gmail.com
- ★ +95 09793449588 Available on WhatsApp
- ★ No 135(5B), Pathein Myay (5) Street, Dawbon Township,

Yangon, Myanmar



SUMMARY

I am a passionate Hybrid Mobile developer with a Bachelor degree in computer science. I have over 4 years' experience in Mobile development. I have accomplished a lot of local and international applications using Ionic and Flutter. I am constantly striving to learn new technologies and look to better myself in the rapidly changing industry. I am interested in learning, contributing and improving day by day, taking part in teamwork. I am always willing to accept new challenges and actively seek out new technologies and stay up-to-date on IT trends.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Nov 2015	University of Computer Studies, Thaton (UCST) Bachelor of Computer Science (B.C.Sc)
Nov 2016	India-Myanmar Centre for Enhancement of IT Skills Professional Diploma in Java Programming Course
Jan 2017	India-Myanmar Centre for Enhancement of IT Skills Professional Certificate in Web Programming Course
Mar 2017	India-Myanmar Centre for Enhancement of IT Skills Professional Certificate in Android Programming Course
Nov 2020	Myanmar IT Consulting PHP Web Developer Bootcamp

EXPERIENCES

Senior Mobile Developer — Source Code Co.,Ltd.

Nov 2023 – Present

- ★ Design and build mobile applications using Flutter.
- ★ Follow the user requirements and designs.
- ★ Ensure code quality, performance and comfort for both Android and IOS.
- ★ Unit Testing, Integration Testing and Maintenance for applications performance improvement.
- ★ Deliver projects on time, with high quality.
- ★ Solve issues quickly.
- ★ Publish android/iOS applications to Google Play Store/Apple App Store.

- ★ Design and build mobile applications using Flutter.
- ★ Follow the user requirements and designs.
- ★ Ensure code quality, performance and comfort for both Android and IOS.
- ★ Unit Testing and Integration Testing for applications performance improvement.
- ★ Deliver projects on time, with high quality.
- ★ Solve issues quickly.
- ★ Publish android/iOS applications to Google Play Store/Apple App Store.

Senior Mobile Developer — Blue City Company

Dec 2020 - Dec 2021

- ★ Design and build mobile applications using Ionic and Flutter.
- ★ Follow the design patterns to keep code maintainable and easily readable
- ★ Ensure code quality, performance and responsiveness of applications
- ★ Write unit tests for code robustness and performance improvement
- ★ Deliver projects on time, with high quality

Mobile Developer — CGM Golden Land Myanmar Company Jan 2019 - Jan 2020

- ★ Design and build mobile applications using Ionic Framework.
- ★ Work on product structure, UI design and app development until the app is released.
- ★ Performed code integration and unit testing with the help of unit test and test apps.

Mobile Developer — Myanmar Information Technology (MIT) May 2017 - Dec 2018

- ★ Design and build mobile applications for Android and iOS platforms with Ionic.
- ★ Work closely with the agile product team to define, design and ship new features.
- ★ Identify and correct bottlenecks and bug fixes.
- ★ Publish android/iOS applications to Google Play Store/Apple App Store.

KEY TECHNICAL SKILLS

- **★** TypeScript
- ★ Css/Scss
- **★** Dart
- ★ PHP
- **★** Java
- ★ Ionic Framework
- **★** Flutter

- ★ RESTful Web Services
- **★** Firebase
- ★ Back4app
- ★ Git
- **★** Backlog
- * Xcode
- ★ Android Studio
- ★ Visual Studio Code

- ★ Object Detection App object detection using TensorFlow model with AI team.
- ★ Self-Coaching App there are many programs that can improve your skills and to meet a new you. You can learn the work techniques of top businessmen in the industry and the knowledge, experience, and thinking of professional coaches. (Based on Japanese language)
- ★ Pre-School App students can record, take photo for their homework and upload files to Dropbox. (Based on Japanese language)
- ★ Thai2d3d App users can bet Thai 2D3D and play KingMaker, Casino, Slots and BTi Sports games.
- ★ Event App event's admin can check users' QR code by mobile QR scanner (online/offline).
- ★ Medical Survey App admin can survey filling form by users' medicine effect after that save data with CSV file.
- ★ B2BMyanmar App users can read up-to-date business news and watch business videos (free or paid).

COMMUNICATION LANGUAGE SKILLS

- **★** Burmese
- ★ English (Pre-Intermediate)
- ★ Japanese (Passed JLPT N5 and Learning N3)